A Guide to the Papers of Frank Whitney Finger, 1880-2002
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- VII: General Files
  - Richmond Schools 1979-1980 (Box 41)
  - Schild 1968-1975 (Box 41)
  - Sciences Organization and Public Relations 1958-1978 (Box 41)
  - Self-Study 1973-1974 (Box 41)
  - Self-Study Summary Report--University of Virginia 1974 Aug (Box 41)
  - Senate Athletic Committee 1979-1983 (Box 41)
  - Sex Discrimination and Opportunities 1979-1980 (Box 41)
  - Sigma XI Files 1965-1966 (Box 41)
  - SSPP Symposium 1951 (Box 41)
  - Sovereign Democracy 1950-1983 (Box 41)
  - Studies of Various Institutions 1968 (Box 41)
  - Suggestions from Buxton 1955 (Box 41)
  - A Survey of Tenured and Non-tenured Faculty in Institutions of Higher Learning in the Southeastern United States Concerning Factors Related to Career Enhancement 1970 (Box 41)
  - Talks on Teaching--Division II Presidential Address 1954-1961 (Box 41)
  - Teaching 1953 (Box 42)
  - Teaching Award Committee 1980-1983 (Box 42)
  - Teaching Psychology 1971-1979, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - "Basic Drives" by Frank Finger and Douglas G. Mook 1962-1970 (Box 42)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award Committee 1981-1983 (Box 42)
  - University of Canterbury 1980-1981 (Box 42)
  - University of Virginia Alumni News 1932 (Box 42)
  - University of North Carolina Chapel Hill 1974 (Box 42)
  - University of Virginia--Related Material 1982 (Box 42)
  - Various Questions--My Answers 1939 (Box 42)
  - Various Talks 1944-1955 (Box 42)
  - Various Talks 1953-1978 (Box 42)
  - Mary Whitney's Courses 1969-1970 (Box 42)
  - Young Men's Christian Association 1952-1953 (Box 42)
- VIII: Personal Papers
  - Boxing--"Official Program, Southern Conference Boxing Tournament, Held at the University of Virginia" 1934 (Box 43)
  - Frank Finger's Competitive Performances 1928-1946 (Box 43)
  - Pilot Log Book 1956-1957 (Box 43)
  - Training Books I and II 1971-1987 (Box 43)
  - Training Books III, IV, and V 1988-1992 (Box 43)
  - Training Book VI (running) 1992-1999 (Box 43)
  - Wrestling--clippings, photographs 1947-1964 (Box 43)
- VIII: Personal Papers, Transcripts
  - Appendices 1940-1998 (Box 43)
  - Bob Brown's Class in Mental Health--speech 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Costa Rica 1995 (Box 43)
  - Diary 1993-1999 (Box 43)
  - Indonesia 1993 (Box 43)
  - Reminiscing 2000, 1 of 3 (Box 43)
  - Reminiscing 2000, 2-3 of 3 (Box 44)
  - Resumes 1915-1992 (Box 44)
  - Retired Faculty Association at the University of Virginia 1995 (Box 44)
  - Scandinavia 1993 (Box 44)
  - Southeastern Psychological Association 1996, 3 folders (Box 44)
  - Travel Essays 1987-1997 (Box 44)
  - Virginia Psychological Association 1996 (Box 44)
  - World War II Diary and Retirement Diary 1939-1941, 1984-89, 2 folders (Box 44)
- IX: Miscellaneous and Restricted Materials
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes; 2 Regarding Abnormal Psychology Lectures; 4 Unidentified 1970s, n.d. (Box 45)
  - Miscellaneous Legal-sized items 1928-1992 (Box 46)
  - Restricted Materials due to F.E.R.P.A. and Privacy Laws 1952-1990 (Box 47-49)
  - Restricted Materials per Donor; Recommendations--Access Totally Restricted for Lifetime of the Subject, or until 2047, Whichever is Longer 1944-1991 (Box 50)